our relationships, but there are also some big problems like Central America, where with
a relatively modest investment, we could really be making a difference and making ourselves
safer.
So there's been this idea of a pivot to Asia.
And what does that mean to you in specific terms?
A transfer of hard military resources, a transfer of sort of time on your agenda in the National
Security Council.
Is it something you've really managed to pull off, or does the Middle East really still
have us kind of sucked in?
I think it means all the above.
Look, Asia is the fastest growing region in the world, the most populous region in the
world, and you've got the largest country in the world, China, that has undergone this
incredible dramatic.